2foodtrippers.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy & Terms of Use

## Privacy Policy

2foodtrippers (https://www.2foodtrippers.com) may request personal information for the purpose of contests, inquiries or orders. We also collect names and email addresses from individuals who choose to subscribe to our email list. This information will not be provided to third parties unless required by law.

### Summary of the Type of Information We Collect and How It Is Used:

#### Information Voluntarily Provided

We collect information that you provide when you sign up for our newsletter or leave a comment on one of our articles. This information is limited to your name and email address.

#### Information Provided by Others

We don’t currently collect information from social networks like Facebook, Instagram and Google. We will update our Privacy Policy if this status changes in the future.

#### Automatically Collected Information

Our website collects certain information about your device when you access the 2foodtrippers website. This information includes your IP address, your operating system type, browser type, referring website, viewed pages and date/time of website access. We may also collect information about the links you click and other actions.

#### Cookies

Our website logs information using cookies which is a standard practice on the internet. These cookies may be session cookies or persistent cookies. If you are uncomfortable with cookies, you can and should clear your browser of cookies at any time.

### How We Use the Collected Information:

  * Operating and maintaining our website
  * Sending promotional information including monthly newsletters. (You can opt out the newsletters at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe button at the bottom of any email.)
  * Sending additional communication as necessary including administrative emails, confirmation emails, technical notices, policy updates and security alerts.
  * Responding to your comments and direct emails.
  * Tracking and measuring the website’s advertising.
  * Protecting the website from unauthorized and/or illegal activity.

### Sharing Your Information with Third Parties

This site uses third-party companies to facilitate the running of the website. However, 2foodtrippers does not provide personal information (i.e. names and email addresses) to these companies. 2foodtrippers is not responsible for the privacy practices of our these companies. We currently use the following third-party providers:

  * **Google Analytics** – website usage tracking
  * **Mail Chimp** – emails and newsletters

We do not share your personal information with other third parties at this time. We will update this Privacy Policy if this status changes.

It is against our policy to sell, distribute, or reveal your email addresses or other personal information without your consent unless we are required to do so by law. This status would change if 2foodtrippers has any of the following occur:  merger, consolidation, acquisition, bankruptcy or reorganization.

### Anonymous Data

We do not currently use anonymous data. This policy may change in the future.

### Publically Visible Information

Your name will be publically visible only if you choose to leave a comment on our website.

### Cookies

The 2foodtrippers site uses cookies to store data about visitors. Third-party services like Google Analytics and Mail Chimp may also use cookies. You always have the right to disable or delete cookies for this and other sites on your internet browser.

### Advertising

#### Display Ads

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve content and advertisements when you visit the 2foodtrippers website. These advertisers may use cookies.

#### **Retargeting  Ads**

We may conduct remarketing efforts with third-party companies like Google, Facebook and Instagram to market the 2foodtrippers website. These companies use cookies to serve ads based on past visits to the website.

#### **Affiliate Program Participation**

We utilize affiliate marketing by embedding tracking links into the 2foodtrippers website. Accordingly, if you click on a link to an affiliate, a cookie will be placed on your browser and will track any sales for calculation of any commissions that result from your purchase.

2foodtrippers is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and links to Amazon.com and its partners.  As part of this Amazon Associates program, 2foodtrippers will post customized links, provided by Amazon, to track the referrals to their website. This program utilizes cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on any eligible sales.

### Newsletters

You may choose to subscribe to our newsletter, which may be used for advertising purposes. All newsletters sent may contain tracking pixels. The pixel is embedded in emails and allows us to analyze the success of online marketing campaigns. Because of these tracking pixels, we may see if and when you open an email and which links within the email you click. Also, this tracking enables us to adapt the content of future newsletters to the interests of the user. This behavior will not be passed on to third parties.

### Rights Related to Your Personal Information

#### Opt-out

You may opt-out of future email communications by following the unsubscribe links in our emails. You may also notify us at info@2foodtrippers.com to be removed from our mailing list.

#### Access

You may access the personal information we have about you by submitting a request to info@2foodtrippers.com.

#### Amend

You may contact us a tinfo@2foodtrippers.com to amend or update your personal information.

#### Forget

You may request that we erase or forget your personal data. To do so, please submit a request to info@2foodtrippers.com.

_Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes or to complete transactions, or when required by law._

### Sensitive Personal Information

You should never submit sensitive personal information to the 2foodtrippers website. Sensitive personal information includes your social security number, information regarding race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, health information, criminal background or trade union memberships. If you elect to submit such information to us, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

### Children’s Information

The 2foodtrippers website does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 16. If a parent or guardian believes that our site has personally identifiable information of a child under the age of 16 in its database, please contact us immediately at info@2foodtrippers.com and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

### Contact Information

Contact us at info@2foodtrippers.com with any questions or concerns related to our privacy policy.

## Terms of Use

All information on this website is for general information and entertainment. Although 2foodtrippers endeavors to have current, correct information, we do not guarantee or warrant that all information is current and correct based on changes that may occur out of our control.

Under no circumstances will 2foodtrippers be liable for any loss or damage including, without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.

## Copyright Policy

All information on this site is subject to copyright law and cannot be used, reprinted or published without written consent.
